freeiva.com 2007-12-10

# China,tour guide,interpreter,exhibition,trade show translator,canton fair,beijing,shanghai,guangzhou

_Privacy Policy_

Freeiva.com ("we," "us").We understand the concerns that you may have about your privacy and respect your right to protect your personal information while online.We may collect certain other personal information from you that we do not post on our Site. In most cases, we do not intentionally transfer this information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent.

We request information from the customer on our booking form and membership form. Here a customer must provide minimum amount of personal information that necessary to make our service happen, including full name,age,gender and your nationality. This information is used for service and billing purposes only.

We will not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. Customer names will not be sold. We will not share your information with third parties although we completely abides by law and will respond to subpoenas, warrants or other court ordersregarding information of a particular customer. Additionally, if a customer/member is believed to be engaged in illegal activity, we reserve the right to report this to law enforcement.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our customers/members are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify customers/members by way of an email. Customers/members will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

By submitting the booking form, I understand that I am expected to comply with laws of the People's Republic of China and to take full and sole legal responsibility for all and any activities in connection with Freeiva's service within China. Otherwise, IVA has right to stop any service and Freeiva refuse refundment.  
  
Copyright (c) 2004 - 2007 Freeiva,Co.,Ltd. All rights reserve   
Company Business Licence No: 3101142111840  
Website ICP Certificate No.05001684 (Shanghai)
